<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>https://ghzghz.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-uk</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 10:43:41 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ghzghz.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Data Migration</title>
      <link>https://ghzghz.github.io/posts/data-migration-details/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 10:43:41 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ghzghz.github.io/posts/data-migration-details/</guid>
      <description>Overview Here are some practical and technical thoughts on planning and executing a data migration project.
They are focused on consumer data from a legacy system as part of a big bang or phased migration; where the discovery, data quality, migration rules, business rules and configuration of the target system is ongoing throughout the project.
ie. sutiable for an agile, iterative and practical approach.
These ideas will hopefully have some relevance for other data migration projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Migration Approach</title>
      <link>https://ghzghz.github.io/posts/data-migration/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 16:47:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ghzghz.github.io/posts/data-migration/</guid>
      <description>Overview I&amp;rsquo;ve worked on many system migration projects over the years in the arena of traditional consumer subscription and billing: cable and satellite and streaming TV, broadband, IP telephony. I wanted to write down some observations on one key aspect of these projects, that of data migration. I intend to describe in detail a technical approach that has worked well for me, as it differs from the more common approaches I have seen and used; although all approaches have pros and cons and no one project is like another.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Post</title>
      <link>https://ghzghz.github.io/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 16:16:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ghzghz.github.io/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This is bold text, and this is emphasized text.
Visit the Hugo website!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
